Comply to survive.
Control is a science fiction, thriller, mystery film directed by James Mark.
A young mother awakens in a mysterious cell and is forced to harness her
telekinetic abilities in order to escape and save her daughter.
Eileen, played by Sara Mitich.
Roger, played by George Tchortov.
Eve, played by Evie Loiselle.
The Administrator, played by Karen LeBlanc.
Men is a 2022 British surrealist folk horror film
written and directed by Alex Garland.
It stars Jessie Buckley as a widow who travels on holiday to a countryside village but becomes
disturbed and tormented by the strange men in the village, all portrayed by Rory Kinnear.
The film was released in the United States on 20 May 2022 by A24 and in the
United Kingdom on 1 June 2022 by Entertainment Film Distributors.
It received generally positive reviews, though its
narrative approach received some criticism.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.